<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Entrepreneurship on Terry Chen</title><link>https://chenterry.com/tags/entrepreneurship/</link><description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on Terry Chen</description><image><title>Terry Chen</title><url>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</url><link>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.136.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chenterry.com/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Product Engineers and AI Multipliers</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/product_engineers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/product_engineers/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img alt="Product Engineers" loading="lazy" src="https://chenterry.com/images/posts/product_engineer/shopify_ai.png">
&lt;em>Tobi Lutke&amp;rsquo;s Shopify internal memo&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="smaller-and-more-efficient-teams">Smaller and More Efficient Teams&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When should we hire a person versus delegating to AI? Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been more reluctant towards hiring people as an attempt to build mid sized projects. Yes, the codebases would get pretty big, and there&amp;rsquo;s also tasks involved that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say are my forte exactly. Yet, when I think about the meetings I have to sit through communicating what I want to build and just time spent doing filler work, I get more and more inclined towards just doing it myself. It&amp;rsquo;s not to say that teamwork isn&amp;rsquo;t good work, some of the most creative product ideas I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on stemmed from chats, during lunch breaks, exploring tangents, with engineers, journalists. The value of connecting the dots during these conversations is something that is difficult to replace. However, is the assumption that delegating work means higher productivity still valid? After all, the cost of execution is continually decreasing (as long as we have a clear idea of what to build).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Craft of Miyazaki in an AI-Generated World</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/interesting_reads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/interesting_reads/</guid><description>&lt;p>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of articles / videos / podcasts that I founding interesting. I&amp;rsquo;ve attached the original article / transcript for easy refernece as well.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="gary-tan-on-manus-the-new-general-purpose-ai-agent">Gary Tan on Manus: The New General-Purpose AI Agent&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Usable AI agents are finally here from deep research platforms out of OpenAI and Google to similar tools from XAI and DeepSeek. Joining the competition now is Manus, a brand new agentic AI platform that has taken the world by storm.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>User Needs &amp; Opportunities</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/user-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/user-needs/</guid><description>&lt;p>When you want to look for user pain points, go to a bar in the middle of the week, look for the most desparate looking person and buy them a beer. They&amp;rsquo;d probably have something substantial to talk about. While I don&amp;rsquo;t usually go to bars during weekdays, I&amp;rsquo;ve found some similar ways of identifying user needs, mostly through conversations or online forums. This is a running document of the user needs or pain points that I&amp;rsquo;ve found to be interesting. Perhaps some of them will turn out to be viable business oppportunities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Crowdlistening</title><link>https://chenterry.com/projects/crowdlistening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/projects/crowdlistening/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="inspiring-insights-amplifying-voices-crowdlisteningcom">Inspiring insights, amplifying voices. (crowdlistening.com)&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;img alt="Webpage" loading="lazy" src="https://chenterry.com/images/posts/crowdlistening/webpage.png">&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="from-content-aggregation-to-original-research">From Content Aggregation to Original Research&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Crowdlistening transforms large-scale social conversations into actionable insight by integrating llm reasoning with extensive model context protocol(MCP) capabilities. Our focus is not just on analyzing content at scale, but rather conducting original research directly from raw social data, generating insights that haven&amp;rsquo;t yet appeared in established reporting.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Deep research features provide professional-looking research reports, yet the contents are far from original, as they&amp;rsquo;re drawn from articles already indexable on the internet and paraphrased with LLMs. However, much of the internet&amp;rsquo;s data exists in unstructured formats - TikTok videos, comments, and metadata, for example. Too much content is generated every day for there to be existing articles written about it all, and when such articles are published, they&amp;rsquo;re often already outdated. When you consider multimodal data, metadata, and connections between data points, these are precisely the types of information that could yield genuinely interesting and useful insights.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Essence of Creativity</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/essense-of-creativity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/essense-of-creativity/</guid><description>&lt;p>This week, I wanted to organize my thoughts about AI-generated content (AIGC) and creativity-related products from the past few months. Rather than focusing solely on my own projects, I&amp;rsquo;d like to explore the foundational aspects of AI product design, interspersing examples from my recent work. First, I want to emphasize that technology is merely a tool intended to better serve business needs. If it doesn&amp;rsquo;t significantly improve efficiency, traditional methods may be more appropriate. Second, despite the many imaginative possibilities of current technology, applications should ultimately be guided by user needs. Finally, AI technologies and markets evolve rapidly, making predictions difficult to validate, but exploring content understanding and generation remains an intriguing challenge.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cogno: Multi-agent AI for sales automation</title><link>https://chenterry.com/archived/cogno/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/archived/cogno/</guid><description>&lt;p>Multi-agent system for cross boarder e-commerce sales automation. Co-founder and head of product.
&lt;a href="https://cognogpt.com">https://cognogpt.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Cogno+ is dedicated to revolutionizing global e-commerce by empowering brands with AI-driven assistance that offers seamless, personalized customer experiences. Our mission is to serve as the digital bridge between brands and customers, enhancing interactions and transactions across international markets, and allowing the brand to increase conversion and upsell while reducing time and money spent on manual customer service.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Multi-agent LLM Systems</title><link>https://chenterry.com/main-themes/multi-agent-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/main-themes/multi-agent-systems/</guid><description>Developing capable multi-agent systems for complex reasoning and human-AI collaboration.</description></item></channel></rss>