<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Prototype on Terry Chen</title><link>https://chenterry.com/categories/prototype/</link><description>Recent content in Prototype on Terry Chen</description><image><title>Terry Chen</title><url>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</url><link>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.136.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chenterry.com/categories/prototype/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Smart Expense Tracker</title><link>https://chenterry.com/archived/smart-expense-tracker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/archived/smart-expense-tracker/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Smart Expense Tracker with Auto-Categorization is a cloud-native application built on AWS serverless architecture. The system automates the tedious process of expense tracking by leveraging AWS services to process receipts, categorize transactions, and provide financial insights. The application offers several key features including receipt scanning and data extraction using AWS Textract, automatic expense categorization with AI (using AWS Bedrock), comprehensive expense tracking, budget setting with automated alerts via SNS, and financial report generation in CSV or PDF formats.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rapid Prototyping of LLM Enabled Webapps</title><link>https://chenterry.com/archived/prototyping/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/archived/prototyping/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="peptalk-ai-journaling-tool">PepTalk: AI Journaling Tool&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Realtime conversation with aI companion to help you note down feelings and journals for the day.
(Prototype: &lt;a href="https://peptalk-navy.web.app/">https://peptalk-navy.web.app/&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what2do-ai-trip-planning-tool">What2Do: AI Trip Planning Tool&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>A trip planning tool for generating itinearies based on article url input and content extraction.
(Prototype: what2do-51224.web.app)&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="ohours-office-hour-scheduling-tool">OHours: Office Hour Scheduling Tool&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>An office hour queuing system to improve student experience and help TAs manage questions more efficiently.
(Prototype: ohours.web.app/)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Credits: Lian Zhang, Janna Lee, Soham Shah, Jonny Kong&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Marrrket: AI Listing Secondhand Marketplace</title><link>https://chenterry.com/archived/marrrket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/archived/marrrket/</guid><description>&lt;p>Marrrket is an AI-powered second-hand marketplace platform targeting North American university students, initially focusing on Chinese international students. The platform aims to solve the inefficiency in the current second-hand market by simplifying the listing process through AI-generated product descriptions from images and minimal user input. By reducing friction in the listing process, Marrrket will increase the overall volume of second-hand items available in the market, creating a more efficient marketplace for both buyers and sellers. The platform&amp;rsquo;s innovation centers on using artificial intelligence to dramatically lower the barrier to entry for sellers, which is hypothesized to be the primary constraint on market growth.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>