<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Research on Terry Chen</title><link>https://chenterry.com/categories/research/</link><description>Recent content in Research on Terry Chen</description><image><title>Terry Chen</title><url>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</url><link>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.136.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chenterry.com/categories/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Realtime Conversational Learning Aid</title><link>https://chenterry.com/archived/groupal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/archived/groupal/</guid><description>&lt;p>Advised by Prof. Kristian Hammond. Developed LLM product that analyzes real-time audio conversations, detects relevancy and misconceptions, and provides targeted Socratic questions and material suggestions through RAG.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Groupal aims to help students work together more effectively and build a deeper understanding in study sessions. The project’s goal is to create a virtual learning assistant that listens to real-time student discussions, detects misconceptions, and facilitates discussions through Socratic questioning techniques and relevant background knowledge retrieval.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Human Quirks</title><link>https://chenterry.com/main-themes/human-quirks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/main-themes/human-quirks/</guid><description>Observing and understanding the strange quirks of individuals and crowds</description></item><item><title>Multi-agent LLM Systems</title><link>https://chenterry.com/main-themes/multi-agent-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/main-themes/multi-agent-systems/</guid><description>Developing capable multi-agent systems for complex reasoning and human-AI collaboration.</description></item><item><title>Data Insights</title><link>https://chenterry.com/main-themes/data-insights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/main-themes/data-insights/</guid><description>Extracting meaningful insights from unstructured multi-modal content.</description></item><item><title>LLM Memory Consolidation and Augmentation</title><link>https://chenterry.com/archived/human-inspired-llm-memory/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/archived/human-inspired-llm-memory/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="a-human-inspired-solution-to-llm-memory-enhancement">A Human-Inspired Solution to LLM Memory Enhancement&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Authors: Terry Chen, Kaiwen Che, Matthew Song&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="abstract">Abstract&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Despite advances in large language model (LLM) capability, their fundamental limitation of not being able to store context over long-lived interactions persists. In this paper, a novel human-inspired three-tiered memory architecture is presented that addresses these limitations through biomimetic design principles rooted in cognitive science. Our approach aligns the human working memory with the LLM context window, episodic memory with vector stores of experience-based knowledge, and semantic memory with structured knowledge triplets.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Improving &amp; Scaling LLMs for Coaching</title><link>https://chenterry.com/projects/improving-scaling-llms-coaching/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/projects/improving-scaling-llms-coaching/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="situated-practice-systems-improving-and-scaling-coaching-through-llms">Situated Practice Systems: Improving and Scaling Coaching through LLMs&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Authors: Terry Chen, Allyson Lee&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="abstract">Abstract&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Effective coaching in project-based learning environments is critical for developing students&amp;rsquo; self-regulation skills, yet scaling high-quality coaching remains a challenge. This paper presents an LLM-enhanced coaching system designed to support project-based learning by helping connect peers struggling with the same regulation gap, and to help coaches by identifying regulation gaps and generating tailored practice suggestions. Our system integrates vector-based semantic matching with LLM-generated regulation gap categorizations for Context Assessment Plan (CAP) notes. Results demonstrate that our system effectively retrieves relevant coaching cases, reducing the cognitive burden on mentors while maintaining high-quality, context-aware feedback.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>