<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Product on Terry Chen</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/</link><description>Recent content in Product on Terry Chen</description><image><title>Terry Chen</title><url>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</url><link>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.136.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chenterry.com/product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Human-Mediated Agentic Workflows</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/agentic_workforce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/agentic_workforce/</guid><description>Explore the emerging landscape of agentic workforces - autonomous AI agents that reason, plan, act, and learn to handle complex tasks and workflows. Analysis of key players, technology strategies, and market opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Search &amp; Discovery Features</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/search/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/search/</guid><description>Development of an intelligent search system using AI and machine learning for enhanced content discovery. Technical implementation, user experience design, and performance optimization for content recommendation platforms.</description></item><item><title>Exploring Unknown Unknowns</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/learning_interface/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/learning_interface/</guid><description>Development of intelligent knowledge interfaces that help users discover unknown unknowns. Technical implementation of AI-powered learning systems and knowledge discovery platforms.</description></item><item><title>AI Content Creation - From Generation to Synthesis</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/personalized_content/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/personalized_content/</guid><description>Moving beyond basic AI summarization to knowledge liquefaction - creating truly personalized learning experiences that adapt content to individual needs, contexts, and cognitive patterns.</description></item><item><title>Improving and Scaling Coaching through LLMs</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/llmcoaching/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/llmcoaching/</guid><description>LLM-enhanced coaching system for project-based learning that scales personalized mentorship through AI. Research on semantic matching, regulation gap identification, and automated coaching suggestions.</description></item><item><title>Content Recommendation Systems</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/recommendation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/recommendation/</guid><description>Development of a multi-modal recommendation system for podcast content using AI and machine learning. Technical architecture, user experience design, and performance analysis for intelligent content discovery.</description></item><item><title>Multi-modal Creative Ad Generation</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/copilot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/copilot/</guid><description>Development of TikTok Symphony Assistant - an AI-powered creative tool for generating ad scripts and video content. Agentic workflows and interface optimization for automated creative generation.</description></item><item><title>Billion Parameter Trend Insight Analysis for Ads</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/insight/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/insight/</guid><description>Development of AI-powered content analysis tools for TikTok trend identification and agency insights. Multi-modal content understanding and actionable trend analysis for advertising agencies.</description></item><item><title>LLM Enabled Homework Helper for All Subjects</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/gauth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/gauth/</guid><description>AI-powered homework assistance platform using advanced LLM reasoning and visualization capabilities across multiple academic subjects to help students learn effectively.</description></item><item><title>An Agentic Social Operating System</title><link>https://chenterry.com/product/crowdlistening/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/product/crowdlistening/</guid><description>Transform large-scale social conversations into actionable insights. Understand crowd sentiment, track emerging opinions, and identify key narratives.</description></item></channel></rss>