<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Terry Chen</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Terry Chen</description><image><title>Terry Chen</title><url>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</url><link>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.136.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chenterry.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Iterating at the Pace of AI</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/agent_prototyping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/agent_prototyping/</guid><description>Two approaches to building agentic experiences: platform-first vs scenario-first. How AI coding tools enable faster prototyping and cross-functional collaboration for agent product development.</description></item><item><title>Social Listening for Product Insight</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/need_validation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/need_validation/</guid><description>Using AI-powered social listening to extract authentic customer insights from online discourse. Moving from product-to-market to market-to-product development through systematic analysis of community discussions.</description></item><item><title>When do I Sunset a Product?</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/sunsetting_projects/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/sunsetting_projects/</guid><description>A framework for deciding when to sunset products and projects. Understanding opportunity costs, sunk cost fallacy, and making difficult decisions about failing ventures.</description></item><item><title>Using LLMs as a Cover up for Poor Thinking</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/poor_thinking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/poor_thinking/</guid><description>How the ease of LLM-generated content masks poor reasoning and why developing domain expertise remains crucial for meaningful innovation beyond automated productivity gains.</description></item><item><title>Questions as the New Bottleneck in Learning</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/asking_questions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/asking_questions/</guid><description>In an age of infinite information, asking the right questions has become more valuable than finding answers. Exploring how question formulation is transforming education and knowledge acquisition.</description></item><item><title>Why People Care What Others Think</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/crowd_thesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/crowd_thesis/</guid><description>Understanding collective intelligence and social dynamics. Why crowd psychology matters for product builders and how human need for belonging drives engagement patterns.</description></item><item><title>Value Add of AI: Generation as Distribution</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/generation_distribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/generation_distribution/</guid><description>Exploring how AI&amp;#39;s greatest value shifts from content creation to personalized distribution and synthesis. From RSS feeds to knowledge liquefaction and the future of adaptive content experiences.</description></item><item><title>Product Engineers and AI Multipliers</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/product_engineers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/product_engineers/</guid><description>How AI is transforming product engineering teams into smaller, more efficient units. Learn why product engineers are becoming more valuable than traditional product managers in AI-first organizations.</description></item><item><title>Interesting Reads</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/interesting_reads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/interesting_reads/</guid><description>Curated collection of compelling articles and insights on AI agents, entrepreneurship, and product development. Features analysis of breakthrough AI tools and emerging trends.</description></item><item><title>The Craft of Miyazaki in an AI-Generated World</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/craft_miyakazi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/craft_miyakazi/</guid><description>Explore Hayao Miyazaki&amp;#39;s meticulous animation process and its significance in today&amp;#39;s AI-generated creative landscape. Learn about the value of craft in a world of automated content.</description></item><item><title>User Needs &amp; Opportunities</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/user-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/user-needs/</guid><description>Identifying real user pain points and business opportunities through conversations and online research. A collection of validated user needs that could become viable startups.</description></item><item><title>2024 in Review</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/year_in_review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/year_in_review/</guid><description>Reflecting on 2024: lessons from founding Cogno, the importance of hands-on product development, choosing college over dropping out, and key insights for first-time founders.</description></item><item><title>How to Work on What You Love</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/advice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/advice/</guid><description>Curated advice from successful entrepreneurs and thinkers on finding passion, going deep on interests, and building a meaningful career doing what you love.</description></item><item><title>Essence of Creativity: Future of Creative Work</title><link>https://chenterry.com/posts/essense_of_creativity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/posts/essense_of_creativity/</guid><description>Exploring the intersection of AI-generated content and human creativity. Analysis of creative workflows, multimodal interactions, and the future of content creation in the AI era.</description></item></channel></rss>