<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Work on Terry Chen</title><link>https://chenterry.com/categories/work/</link><description>Recent content in Work on Terry Chen</description><image><title>Terry Chen</title><url>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</url><link>https://chenterry.com/images/profile.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.136.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chenterry.com/categories/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Insight Spotlight</title><link>https://chenterry.com/projects/insight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/projects/insight/</guid><description>&lt;p>Analyze thousands of tiktoks to provide actionable trends &amp;amp; insights for key agencies. (Worked on multi-modal content understanding)
To be released on TikTok Creative Center (&lt;a href="https://ads.tiktok.com/business/creativecenter/pc/en">https://ads.tiktok.com/business/creativecenter/pc/en&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Credits: TikTok Creative Team&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="beyond-data-the-evolution-of-ai-driven-insight-products-for-content-creation">Beyond Data: The Evolution of AI-Driven Insight Products for Content Creation&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="introduction-the-shifting-landscape-of-creative-ai-tools">Introduction: The Shifting Landscape of Creative AI Tools&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In the rapidly evolving space of AI-driven creative tools, we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing a significant transition from general-purpose large language models to specialized, task-specific agent systems. This shift represents a fundamental change in how AI approaches creative work, particularly in advertising and marketing.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Symphony Assistant</title><link>https://chenterry.com/projects/copilot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://chenterry.com/projects/copilot/</guid><description>&lt;p>Leverage generative AI capabilities for creative script ideation and video ad creation. (Worked on agentic workflows and interface optimization)
&lt;a href="https://ads.tiktok.com/business/copilot/standalone?locale=en&amp;amp;deviceType=pc">https://ads.tiktok.com/business/copilot/standalone?locale=en&amp;amp;deviceType=pc&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Credits: TikTok Creative Team&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="building-agentic-workflows">Building Agentic Workflows&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="from-llms-to-agents">From LLMs to Agents&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The transition from LLMs to Agents has become a consensus in the AI community, representing an improvement in complex task execution capabilities. However, helping users fully utilize Agent capabilities to achieve tenfold efficiency gains requires careful workflow design. These workflows aren&amp;rsquo;t merely a presentation of parallel capabilities, but seamless integrations with human-in-the-loop quality assurance. This document uses Typeface as a reference to explain why a clear primary workflow is necessary, as well as design approaches for functional extensions.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>